So, next time we're transforming into
Julia and Annamie
I think she's the youngest member in
the group, but she's definitely the
smartest.
She's smart.
Hard.
She's in hard mode.
Hard mode.
English hard mode.
I see.
This program is a program in which six
people who are active to promote
something exciting challenge various
things to raise the excitement value of
the world.
Thank you.
Yelling at me
Yes, all white on top
I'm sorry.
I'm suspicious of you.
You did something bad.
I'm wrong.
I thought you were a good person.
I'm not good at it.
You are.
I'm using a GoPro as a PC.
I'm worried if this video is published.
I'm sorry.
I'm kidding.
Thank you for watching this video.
Oh, come on.
Oh, this is... I'm sorry.
This is my room for a meeting.
Meeting room?
I have a meeting here.
Ah, no.
Oh, okay. I guess my meeting is later.
Maybe.
I think I have a meeting here.
Sorry.
But you guys are really so cute.
No, no.
Thank you.
This is you guys?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah? Wait, which one is you?
This is mine.
Oh, that's you?
Why are you so big?
Yeah.
What was it?
New member.
Oh, new face.
When did you join?
Last October.
Oh, wow, very new. When did you join?
Two years ago.
Oh, what's your name?
My name is Julia.
Oh, Julia.
My name is Bambi.
Bambi.
Yes, so good.
So your name is Juliet.
So you speak English?
No, I can't.
Your parents are Japanese?
Yes.
Wow, so she spoke to you in English?
I'm a dancer.
Oh, okay, wow.
So what are your hobbies?
Hobbies?
My hobby is...
What is it?
Sleeping?
Hobbies are sleeping.
Ballet.
Oh, ballet.
And swimming.
What's the name of this group?
Tokimeki Senden.
Oh.
Thank you.
Publicity.
Tokimeki means publicity.
Senden means publicity.
Oh, ok. What is Tokimeki?
Tokimeki...
I don't know.
Tokimeki means...
Happiness?
Heart attack?
I don't know...
But I don't feel anything.
Spark!
Tokimeki!
I don't know what it is, but Tokimeki!
Something special?
Tokimeki?
I don't know what it is.
Oh, when you feel like really like a
sparkle or something.
What were you up to yesterday?
Yesterday?
What were you up to last night?
Last night?
Last night
But you know the meaning of it?
You're amazing!
That's a little different
I was reading the living
What was it?
Magazine
Magazine? Comic?
Oh, okay
How do you like to spend your time
though?
You were doing homework last night, but
how do you like to spend your time?
I like to spend my time
Watching TV
Oh, okay, you watch
Alright, so are you ready for the Tokyo
Olympics?
Tokyo Olympics?
How would you introduce yourself in
English?
Introduce myself?
Yeah
Wow!
My name is Julia. I'm 15 years old. My
hobby is ballet.
And my... my favorite actress is May
Nagano.
Ah! You're so ready!
Yeah! You're perfect.
My name is Ban... Banbi Fujimoto.
Ban... Banbi Fujimoto.
I'm 14 years old.
My hobby is swimming and sleeping.
Oh!
And reading... reading books.
Wow! You're amazing!
And Julia.
My actress... my favorite actress is
May Nagano and Ayase Haruka.
Oh! And who?
Ayase Haruka.
Ayase Haruka. I don't know.
So, what's your favorite food?
Potato!
Potato?
French fries!
Oh, yeah! French fries.
French fries.
Me too! I love French fries!
I love garlic French fries.
Garlic.
Do you know garlic?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Garlic.
Do you like garlic?
Yeah.
What in the world.
Thank you!
Let's go!
Where are you from?
What?
What country?
Not what, where are you from?
Where are you from?
I'm from California.
California?
Yeah, California.
Where are you living now?
I live here now.
Yeah.
How many languages can you speak?
I can speak English.
And Japanese?
Maybe.
I don't know.
And Spanish.
Can you speak Spanish?
Spanish, I know like, how is that?
Gracias.
What did you say?
You're changing the subject.
You always say thank you.
It's a difference in names.
Yay!
Julia is amazing!
She speaks Japanese better than me!
She is so fluent!
I was asking questions in Japanese and
she was speaking in Spanish!
Spanish?
I said thank you.
Gracias!
Amazing!
Why did you do this prank?
What do you think it is?
I think it is related to the Olympics.
Oh!
Tokyo Olympics!
First of all,
I want to show you how good our English
is.
I want to learn more!
We will learn English from now on.
We did it!
Shidani
Yes, Shidani
So, since there is the Olympics, we
will try to talk more
Yes, please take care of us
Please take care of us
It's okay, it's okay
Mio and I are the most dangerous
What should I do?
No, it's here
It's dangerous
It was pretty bad
It's okay, it's okay
It's floating.
Hello, everyone watching TOKIBARO. I'm
Anjulia.
Tadami Hachimoto.
Nice to meet you. We are Anjulia.
Yeah!
What are we going to do today?
Today, we are going to do this.
Like this.
This is it.
Ta-da!
It's a magic bottle for love.
It's a shaker.
Let's shake it.
Only the people with a pure heart can
see this.
But if you laugh, it's weird.
Your heart may be dirty.
Is it okay?
Please wash it off with water and watch
it again.
Let's wash your heart properly.
This is Julia and Bami.
We are BANJULIA.
If you like this video, please
subscribe to the channel.
This is a video of a person.
What is this?
This is soy sauce.
This is miso.
This is a fox.
This is a ladder.
This is a lemon.
This is a chive.
This is a food that makes you hungry.
We are also hungry.
This is a chive.
Let's have the best summer ever!
Barcelona toast
SIK-K at theoya
I love you, S Jews!!
DM in ENG
Miyume's D1 MC